好的，我还没有发布这堂课，但是这本超过200页的书
all right I have not posted this lecture yet it's more than 200 pages and I
yet it's more than 200 pages and I almost have only 10 pages left you know
几乎只剩下10页了，所以让我们打开心理导师吧，我是
almost have only 10 pages left you know so let's open the mentary stop so I'm
so let's open the mentary stop so I'm going to be jumping through but I will
将要跳过，但我今天将尝试完成最后十页
going to be jumping through but I will try to finish the last ten pages today
try to finish the last ten pages today and post them by the end of the day so I
并在一天结束前发布它们，所以我认为所有项目都已经完成
and post them by the end of the day so I assume all the projects have been
assume all the projects have been submitted including from those who have
提交，包括那些没有计划提交项目的人，并且
submitted including from those who have no plans to submit project all right and
no plans to submit project all right and so we have permission projects and the
所以我们有许可项目，截止日期是昨天还可以，所以我们需要
so we have permission projects and the deadline was yesterday okay so we need
deadline was yesterday okay so we need project all right so we're going to do
好的项目，所以我们要做的是，我要经历一下
project all right so we're going to do is I'm going to go through you know
is I'm going to go through you know notice there is another point mental
请注意，今天我还有另一点精神状态，因为我超过一百万
notice there is another point mental state today because I'm over a million
state today because I'm over a million things when we are trying to jump
当我们试图跳越飞机以确保我们掩盖了一切
things when we are trying to jump through the flight to be sure we cover
through the flight to be sure we cover some essential topics and depending on
一些基本主题，并根据我们的位置，我们在星期四决定是否
some essential topics and depending on where we are we decide on Thursday if we
where we are we decide on Thursday if we continue this lecturer would jump to
继续，这位讲师会跳到状态空间模型，幻灯片非常
continue this lecturer would jump to state-space models the slides are very
state-space models the slides are very easy so you guys can read them in detail
容易，所以你们可以详细阅读它们，所以我将尝试做一些事情
easy so you guys can read them in detail so I'm gonna try to to do some something
so I'm gonna try to to do some something here there so things I want to discuss
在这里，所以我今天想讨论的事情希望我们将有时间做
here there so things I want to discuss today hopefully we will have time to do
today hopefully we will have time to do this how do we complete parameters in
这如何在hmm模型和计算参数中完成参数
this how do we complete parameters in hmm models and in computing parameters
hmm models and in computing parameters we will see that we need to integrate
我们将看到我们需要集成用于前进和后退的算法
we will see that we need to integrate the algorithms for forward and backward
the algorithms for forward and backward passing message passing basically those
传递消息基本上传递那些消息将是必不可少的
passing message passing basically those messages will serve as essential
messages will serve as essential statistics that will allow us to
统计数据，使我们能够在进行一些培训后完成参数设置
statistics that will allow us to complete parameters given some training
complete parameters given some training data okay
数据好多少，所以我要
data okay what number was so I'm going to be
what number was so I'm going to be jumping slide and I'm going to go we
跳幻灯片，我要走了，我们停止了幻灯片21的最后一次演讲，所以我们
jumping slide and I'm going to go we stopped last lecture on slide 21 so we
stopped last lecture on slide 21 so we can deal extinct
可以用马尔可夫模型处理简单的灭绝训练
can deal extinct simple training with a Markov model okay
保守地讲，基本上学习怜悯的问题包括
conservatively the the problem of learning basically mercy consists of
learning basically mercy consists of words and I'm going to introduce some
单词，我将介绍一个单词的一些概率模型，因此
words and I'm going to introduce some probability models over a single word so
时间是时间的信息暗示了句子中的顺序，所以不是
information the time is time implies sequence in a sentence okay so it's not
sequence in a sentence okay so it's not really I mean you can apply this as
真的，我的意思是说您可以在说话没问题时将其应用为反对，所以这
really I mean you can apply this as opposed when you talk alright so this
opposed when you talk alright so this can be represented once at the given
可以在给定的时间代表一次，但现在是
can be represented once at the given time but right now is world within a
time but right now is world within a text question so this is what we call
文字问题，所以这就是我们所说的英格拉姆（Ingram）概率，这是一个二元组
text question so this is what we call the Ingram probability this is a bigram
the Ingram probability this is a bigram probability so what's the next word
概率，那么下一个单词将被赋予前一个世界，
probability so what's the next word going to be given the previous world and
going to be given the previous world and this is what is the next word given the
这是给定前两个词的下一个词是什么
this is what is the next word given the previous two words
previous two words so we can train a model like that given
所以我们可以训练一个像给定数据的模型，并做一些电路基础的
so we can train a model like that given data and do some circuit elementary
data and do some circuit elementary statistics
统计数据和一些先前的建模来做到这一点
statistics with some prior modeling to do that this
with some prior modeling to do that this is an essential problem if you are
如果您有兴趣完成句子，则是一个基本问题，如果
is an essential problem if you are interested to complete the sentence if
interested to complete the sentence if you want to compress basically text and
您想基本上压缩文本，也想自动编写
you want to compress basically text and also if you want to write automatically
also if you want to write automatically without you know any interference from a
在您不知道任何人为干扰的情况下，您想在逗留期间写
without you know any interference from a human you want to write in a stay which
human you want to write in a stay which of course may not be reading anything
当然可能没有阅读任何内容，但是您知道是否需要任何内容
of course may not be reading anything but you know if you want anything
but you know if you want anything somebody will buy okay so this is
有人会买的好，所以这是教科书好吧，有些错过了
somebody will buy okay so this is textbook all right some missed an
textbook all right some missed an example of this probabilities of the
不同的Engram概率的此概率示例
example of this probabilities of the Engram probabilities for the different
Engram probabilities for the different letters they enjoyed in the alphabet and
他们在字母表中喜欢的字母，第一个字母基本上意味着
letters they enjoyed in the alphabet and the first letter is basically implies
the first letter is basically implies nothing unknown so as timber basically
没有什么不知道的，所以这些符号内根本不存在木材
nothing unknown so as timber basically doesn't exist within those symbols this
doesn't exist within those symbols this is the Biograph probabilities to
是传记人物从一个字母转换为另一个字母的概率
is the Biograph probabilities to transition from one letter to another
transition from one letter to another the biggest this white spaces the high
这个空白最大，这个概率门的高度很高，所以这有点
the biggest this white spaces the high of this probability door so this is sort
of this probability door so this is sort of like a kingdom diagram
就像一个王国图，所以我们将要欺骗
of like a kingdom diagram so we're going to have trick to the
so we're going to have trick to the mathematical problem and we will try to
数学问题，我们将尝试在句子的上下文中进行解释
mathematical problem and we will try to explain this in the context of sentences
explain this in the context of sentences the algebra but a very sort of universal
代数，但即使对于隐马尔可夫模型，也具有很强的通用性
the algebra but a very sort of universal even for hidden Markov models that he
even for hidden Markov models that he understands this we can understand a
了解这一点，我们可以了解一些更复杂的专业模型
understands this we can understand a little bit more complex pro model the
little bit more complex pro model the Markov chain is rather hidden Markov
马尔可夫链是相当隐蔽的马尔可夫模型，所以我们有了下一个Ronix
Markov chain is rather hidden Markov model right so we have it's a next Ronix
model right so we have it's a next Ronix to our X capital T so using conditional
到我们的X大写T，所以使用条件独立关系，我们喜欢这样
to our X capital T so using conditional independence relations we like this like
independence relations we like this like that this is the probability of the
这是初始状态的概率，所以给定了这个
that this is the probability of the initial state so this is given and this
initial state so this is given and this of the transition probabilities from
从状态X到您的XT过渡概率的总和-减去1到XT
of the transition probabilities from state X want you to XT minus 1 to X T
state X want you to XT minus 1 to X T and I can run a test in a much nicer
我可以用您在第三种方法中看到的更好的格式进行测试
and I can run a test in a much nicer format the way that you see on the third
format the way that you see on the third lines I want you to pay close attention
我希望您密切注意这些行，因为这种表示法非常
lines I want you to pay close attention because sort of the notation is very
because sort of the notation is very standard these are many other problems
标准这些是混合模型之类的许多其他问题，所以您
standard these are many other problems for mixed models and and the like so you
for mixed models and and the like so you know this is a standard way to write the
知道在给定的情况下这是写联合概率分布的标准方法
know this is a standard way to write the joint probability distribution given the
joint probability distribution given the parameters and parameters here referring
参数和参数在这里指的是初始的概率
parameters and parameters here referring to the probability the initial
to the probability the initial probabilities of being upstaged a and
升级的概率a和过渡概率可能带有
probabilities of being upstaged a and the transition probabilities may carry
the transition probabilities may carry transitioning from state a to state K so
从状态a过渡到状态K，所以再看一遍，这是否有意义
transitioning from state a to state K so look at this again does this make sense
look at this again does this make sense is this the same as what we see up there
这和我们在那里看到的一样吗
所以你怎么理解现在看不到x1的概率
look at this again does this make sense is this the same as what we see up there
so how do you understand can't see the probability of x1 now this is written
所以你怎么理解现在看不到x1的概率
probability of x1 now this is written like that so what does not mean the big
这样的话，这并不意味着指标功能就大了，所以它是
like that so what does not mean the big is the indicator function right so it's
is the indicator function right so it's Rondo and the argument is school zero
回旋曲和论点是学校零
Rondo and the argument is school zero otherwise
otherwise so as this don't do here addiction is on
所以在这里不做瘾，所以上瘾就在一种状态，那么我有一个空间
so as this don't do here addiction is on state one right then I have a space for
state one right then I have a space for a lot of times
很多时候，如果x1等于
a lot of times so if x1 is equal to let's say is the
so if x1 is equal to let's say is the state Z so this time what will give me
状态Z，所以这次会给我什么，你会给我PJ，如果x1不是a
state Z so this time what will give me you will give me PJ and if x1 isn't a
you will give me PJ and if x1 isn't a means x1 is not in all the other states
表示x1不在其他所有状态，因此如果执行此过程，则所有尝试都将
means x1 is not in all the other states so if this process all the attempts will
so if this process all the attempts will give me basically a power of 0 which
基本上给我0的幂，好吧，结果为1好吧，所以这
give me basically a power of 0 which will result to 1 okay all right so this
will result to 1 okay all right so this is the way to write P of x1 and
是写x1的P的方法，
句子，每个句子的长度都是T，没错，所以这是税收上要说的
will result to 1 okay all right so this is the way to write P of x1 and
sentences each with length T all right so this is the one would say in tax but
句子，每个句子的长度都是T，没错，所以这是税收上要说的
so this is the one would say in tax but has okay so this is a point remove a
没关系，所以这是一个重点，删除一个序列，这是一个很漂亮的
has okay so this is a point remove a sequence this is a beautiful in the
sequence this is a beautiful in the states of J and K and this probability
J和K的状态，以及说JK到此的转变概率
states of J and K and this probability of transitions to say JK to this
of transitions to say JK to this indicator function transitioning from J
指标函数从T的J减1到K以及对
indicator function transitioning from J of T minus 1 to K and what interested to
of T minus 1 to K and what interested to compute a JK I mean most of the things
计算一个JK，我的意思是直到现在我们已经完成了大部分工作，我们假设
compute a JK I mean most of the things we have done up to now we assume that
we have done up to now we assume that this parameters are known now we don't
现在我们知道这些参数，我们将不知道这些参数。
this parameters are known now we don't know these parameters and we're going to
know these parameters and we're going to compute them from data so interesting
从数据中计算它们，所以有趣的是
compute them from data so interesting here will be
here will be this one will it's a sequence of words
这将是一个冗长的单词序列，但现在我要
this one will it's a sequence of words of lengthy but now I'm going to have any
of lengthy but now I'm going to have any sequence of words each of them having
单词的顺序，每个单词的长度都正确，所以我要
sequence of words each of them having length all right so I'm going to
length all right so I'm going to basically text of different lengths so
基本上是不同长度的文本，所以x1我们执行了一个冗长的单词
basically text of different lengths so x1 we have a lengthy one words executed
x1 we have a lengthy one words executed 2 etc but if you not you can take that
2等等，但是如果您不这样做，则可以认为每一个的长度都相同
2 etc but if you not you can take that the length of each of this is the same
the length of each of this is the same so the is given semester of the logs i
所以给定了学期的日志，我给出了theta，我正在那样做
so the is given semester of the logs i given theta and i'm making it like that
given theta and i'm making it like that so i want you to look hard from this
所以我想让您从这个方程式中仔细观察第三行
so i want you to look hard from this equation the third line a went to the
equation the third line a went to the nothing to it questions this make sense
毫无疑问，这是有道理的
来描述估计轮渡员，这是我所有的数据集，我将其推入了工作中
equation the third line a went to the nothing to it questions this make sense
to describe estimation ferrymen which is all my data sets i push it in the works
来描述估计轮渡员，这是我所有的数据集，我将其推入了工作中
all my data sets i push it in the works okay and I left the summation so maybe
好吧，我离开了总结部分，所以也许人们预定了这种进步，
okay and I left the summation so maybe people books this progress ever becomes
people books this progress ever becomes summation right so I first destination
求和正确，所以我首先要到达外面的州
summation right so I first destination over the states outside and this
over the states outside and this summation over the data sets they push
如果我上了这个学期，我会将它们推入其中的数据集的总和
summation over the data sets they push it inside should I get on this term I
it inside should I get on this term I get this all right and in this term I'm
一切都好，在这个学期中，我将求和推算
get this all right and in this term I'm going to push the summation over n an
going to push the summation over n an estimation over the length of verse
估计里面的句子长度，然后
estimation over the length of verse sentences inside and then the
sentences inside and then the estimations over the states I will leave
对状态的估计我会把它们留在外面，通常不会错过
estimations over the states I will leave them outside and the usually not missus
them outside and the usually not missus blaze what I mean is I'm colorblind so
我的意思是说我是色盲，所以这不是我在做的原因，因为我
blaze what I mean is I'm colorblind so it's not like I'm doing it because I
it's not like I'm doing it because I enjoy a lot right so what's the reason
享有很多权利，所以我们在这里标记它们的原因是什么，所以
enjoy a lot right so what's the reason we mark them for a reason here so what
we mark them for a reason here so what you see this mr. blue colors what are
你看到这个先生。蓝色它们对于这个国家的参数是什么
you see this mr. blue colors what are they for this nation of the parameters
they for this nation of the parameters theta Mr mouse won't know whether we
theta Mr mouse不会知道我们是否要称呼它
theta Mr mouse won't know whether we gonna call this
这是来自数据的信息的来源，因此估算
this is where the information from the data comes so in estimating this part of
data comes so in estimating this part of the speed day and alpha JK the only
速度日和Alpha JK唯一需要我们知道的信息
the speed day and alpha JK the only information we need this to know this
information we need this to know this quantity this can be so rapidly how do
数量如此之快，我们如何称呼它们
quantity this can be so rapidly how do we call them
原则上很好的证据证明了这项权利的消解，这是今天的证据
well in principle evidence dissolve this right this is the evidence of the day
right this is the evidence of the day cow so but the very top the bank as
因此，但作为独立实体的银行最高层却有权
cow so but the very top the bank as independent entities excise a right they
independent entities excise a right they come in making the parameters theta
通过任何方式将参数theta放入这些大的求和中
come in making the parameters theta inside those big summations by anything
inside those big summations by anything we need to know the individual data we
我们需要知道单个数据，我们需要知道这些总和，所以这
we need to know the individual data we need to know these summations so this
need to know these summations so this summation is in blue or what mister
汇总显示为蓝色或错误的患者统计数据，因此您将需要此
summation is in blue or what mister patient statistics so you will need this
patient statistics so you will need this to know this blue quantities so I am
知道这个蓝色数量，所以我要去参加j1的国会，我要
to know this blue quantities so I am going to Congress than j1 and I'm gonna
going to Congress than j1 and I'm gonna call this and JK so which words can you
叫这个和JK，这样你能告诉我什么不是有人在看着
call this and JK so which words can you tell me what isn't anyone so looking at
tell me what isn't anyone so looking at this body that's you know miss baptize
你知道这个身体，小姐为它施洗了一些东西，因为有一个J
this body that's you know miss baptize it something and j1 because there's a J
it something and j1 because there's a J there there's no I I'm summing Ally and
我没有对Ally进行求和，因为这是指1号州（美洲）
there there's no I I'm summing Ally and because this refers to state 1 Americas
because this refers to state 1 Americas and J 1 so what is this in words what
和J 1那么这是什么意思发送L 1的意思呢？
and J 1 so what is this in words what sends L 1 I mean obviously mister
sends L 1 I mean obviously mister indicator function some looking at all
指标功能一些可以查看所有数据，我正在考虑
indicator function some looking at all the data all right and I'm accounting in
the data all right and I'm accounting in my data set so I have n of laws and
我的数据集，所以我有n个法律和苏丹这支军队占了多少
my data set so I have n of laws and sultans this arm accounting how many
sultans this arm accounting how many times what
乘什么
第一部分在网络状态下，我们应该采取一个，我在数
sultans this arm accounting how many times what
the first segment is on the web state we should take one and I'ma counting how
第一部分在网络状态下，我们应该采取一个，我在数
should take one and I'ma counting how many times the state one is or what one
状态是多少次，或者说某个特定的马卡蒂状态是多少
many times the state one is or what one say some particular Makati how many
say some particular Makati how many times the first and the first world in
最终文件中的第一个和第一个世界是那个特定的战争
times the first and the first world in the end documents is that particular war
the end documents is that particular war okay this is again next refers to the
好吧，这又是下一个指的是数据三分之一对，这是状态一
okay this is again next refers to the data thirds right this is the state one
data thirds right this is the state one of each of the sentences I remind you x1
我记得每个句子中的x1是长度为TI的句子
of each of the sentences I remind you x1 is a sentence of length TI all right
is a sentence of length TI all right x10 is another long sentence of words of
x10是长度为TI的另一个长句子，可以将所有首字母大写
x10 is another long sentence of words of length T I am okay to capitulate all
length T I am okay to capitulate all right what is the symbol now what is
对，现在的符号是什么？这个足够的统计量是什么，所以我来了
right what is the symbol now what is this sufficient statistic so I'm coming
this sufficient statistic so I'm coming over other data over all the words in it
在此X 1到X的每个数据集中的所有单词上的其他数据之上
over other data over all the words in it data set in each of this X 1 to X
data set in each of this X 1 to X capital N and I'm accounting work in
大写N，我在这些句子中从事会计工作
capital N and I'm accounting work in those sentences some accounting in all
those sentences some accounting in all my data how many times a time T I was
我的数据是TI从状态J开始的时间是多少，而T加上1的时间我是
my data how many times a time T I was from state J and the time T plus 1 I was
from state J and the time T plus 1 I was of state K all right so we have two
的状态K没关系，所以我们有两个版本，权利T的多少倍
of state K all right so we have two versions right how many times the pay T
versions right how many times the pay T was the what J and how many times the
是J以及同时陈述的最多一次是多少次
was the what J and how many times the stated most one simultaneously was on
stated most one simultaneously was on state K I can the log-likelihood as
状态KI可以将对数可能性作为这些足够的统计时间而无需
state K I can the log-likelihood as these sufficient statistic times without
these sufficient statistic times without sufficient statistic and I do alright I
足够的统计数据，我确实可以，我没有时间进行
sufficient statistic and I do alright I don't have time to go through the
don't have time to go through the algebra but I want you to look sort of
代数，但我希望您看起来像个视觉
algebra but I want you to look sort of visual
visual we do now to find the parameters by Jay
我们现在要做的是找到Jay和DJ Kay的参数，这有点通用
we do now to find the parameters by Jay and DJ Kay this is sort of a generic
and DJ Kay this is sort of a generic inference problem called discrete
推理问题称为离散分布，因此您应该有一些
inference problem called discrete distributions so you should have some
distributions so you should have some good idea on how to do this so how do
关于如何执行此操作的好主意，如何计算加速Aryan的功能
good idea on how to do this so how do you compute this power that speeds Aryan
you compute this power that speeds Aryan alpha DK I give you the results are
alpha DK我给你的结果是在我的模型中最大化的
alpha DK I give you the results are coming in my model maximizing the
coming in my model maximizing the evidence cause we're gonna take
证据表明，我们将针对Phi J和
evidence cause we're gonna take derivatives with respect to Phi J and
derivatives with respect to Phi J and alpha J carry in taking the remnants of
阿尔法J携带关于Phi J的残余物
alpha J carry in taking the remnants of this with respect to Phi J you also have
this with respect to Phi J you also have to enhance this with something else
用其他方法来增强此效果，因为PI J不是独立的
to enhance this with something else because the PI J's are not independent
because the PI J's are not independent of each other if you take the sum over I
彼此的总和如果我拿走总和，我的意思是说在某种状态下
of each other if you take the sum over I mean at some state so the terrified
mean at some state so the terrified zatia's to be equal to one alright so
扎蒂亚等于一个好，所以我们需要做的是，我们需要发送
zatia's to be equal to one alright so that we need to do is we need to send
that we need to do is we need to send additional grants multiplier to enforce
额外的赠款乘数来强制孩子们必须在这里添加一个
additional grants multiplier to enforce the children gonna have to add here a
the children gonna have to add here a term 1/2 times the summation of the Phi
学期的Phi J的总和的1/2倍将跑到K-Ronnie
term 1/2 times the summation of the Phi J's for take will run to K - Ronnie
J's for take will run to K - Ronnie right
正确的
我们对PI J的看法也有所不同，包括您将获得的期限
J's for take will run to K - Ronnie right
and we take also vary with respect to PI J including the term you will get this
我们对PI J的看法也有所不同，包括您将获得的期限
J including the term you will get this and partial derivative with respect to a
以及关于JK的偏导数，您将获得业务
and partial derivative with respect to a JK you will get that the business will
JK you will get that the business will collapse this are central to the obvious
崩溃，这是显而易见答案的关键，所以您说我不必做
collapse this are central to the obvious answer so you say I do not have to do
answer so you say I do not have to do any calculations because I know what the
任何计算，因为我知道答案会是什么，但显然我们
any calculations because I know what the answer is going to be but obviously we
answer is going to be but obviously we need this methodology for more complex
需要这种方法来解决更复杂的问题，所以在这个项目中
need this methodology for more complex problems so with this project
problems so with this project what was the physical meaning offends
物理意义是什么又冒犯了任何人
what was the physical meaning offends anyone again
在我的数据集中，有多少次第一步被向上除以
there is how many times in my data sets the step one was upwards I divide it by
the step one was upwards I divide it by how many times I was on anything on
我在某州做过多少次某事，让我们采取一种红色，一种就好
how many times I was on anything on state one let's take one red one okay
state one let's take one red one okay and counting how many times to hit
并计算从国庆日到携带的过渡次数
and counting how many times to hit transitions from state day to carry
transitions from state day to carry visitors you know how many times I have
访客，您知道我已经从a过渡到任何可以的次数
visitors you know how many times I have transitioned from as a to whatever okay
transitioned from as a to whatever okay it is really significant transitions
从人民到任何活跃的交流的真正重要转变
it is really significant transitions from the people to whatever active comm
from the people to whatever active comm transitions from stage a is this the
从阶段a过渡是j2的归一化因子
transitions from stage a is this the normalization factor from j2 anything
normalization factor from j2 anything else so actually to make it sort of more
否则实际上是为了使它更好一点，然后看着您放了K素数
else so actually to make it sort of more nice and looking at you put the K prime
nice and looking at you put the K prime there and K Prime this result okay this
那里和K Prime这个结果好吧，这个模型在计算上非常
there and K Prime this result okay this models are computationally very
models are computationally very difficult to work with because we
很难使用，因为我们介绍了您
difficult to work with because we introduced this probabilities that you
introduced this probabilities that you here for improve immediately basically
在这里立即进行改进，基本上就像我们从推论中所做的一样
here for improve immediately basically like what we did with the inference from
like what we did with the inference from with the parameter estimation problem
与参数估计问题有关，我们只需要制作多少个参数
with the parameter estimation problem how many parameters we have just to make
how many parameters we have just to make theory each of the states it's K
理论每个状态都是K
消息说，我们计算了如果这是K和KT平方的年数
how many parameters we have just to make theory each of the states it's K
the message saying that we computed how many years if this is K and K T squared
消息说，我们计算了如果这是K和KT平方的年数
many years if this is K and K T squared all right so if you have an engine
好吧，如果您有一个发动机社区，这将是力量的K
all right so if you have an engine community this will be K to the power n
community this will be K to the power n so this is computationally very
所以这在计算上非常昂贵，并且数据集和我
so this is computationally very expensive and the wrong data sets and I
expensive and the wrong data sets and I was moving actually the other day so one
前几天实际上在移动，所以其中一个稍后说，但是您可以下载
was moving actually the other day so one of those later says but you can download
of those later says but you can download as 30,000 words and the number of profit
30,000字，利润的数量基本上是用来校准模型的，
as 30,000 words and the number of profit is basically to calibrate the model and
is basically to calibrate the model and this term diagram model is 2.5 billion
这个术语图模型是25亿个参数，实际上这并非微不足道
this term diagram model is 2.5 billion parameters actually this is not trivial
parameters actually this is not trivial because you know the model is not
因为您知道模型在计算上并不昂贵，所以不是
because you know the model is not computationally expensive so it's not we
computationally expensive so it's not we need to go away from maximizing the
需要远离最大化数据的可能性，也许
need to go away from maximizing the likelihood of the data and maybe do
likelihood of the data and maybe do something Bayesian here so this can be
贝叶斯在这里，所以这可以给我的情况下，模型
something Bayesian here so this can be give me the situation where the model
give me the situation where the model that we discussed will not work so you
我们讨论过的方法将无法正常工作，因此您需要将意大利语中的数据与
that we discussed will not work so you have the Italian the data with a few
have the Italian the data with a few sentences that contain a few words and
包含几个单词的句子，您知道我们计算了过渡
sentences that contain a few words and and you know we computed transition
and you know we computed transition probabilities you know and obviously you
您知道的概率，显然可以进行预测，并且知道
probabilities you know and obviously you can do predictions you know you can and
can do predictions you know you can and I will do it actually hopefully in a few
我实际上希望这样做，几分钟后您就可以预测下一个
I will do it actually hopefully in a few minutes you can predict what the next
minutes you can predict what the next word is going to be but why do we need
这个词将会是，但是为什么我们需要做贝叶斯呢？
word is going to be but why do we need to do Bayesian rather much more likely
to do Bayesian rather much more likely if it's there in the specific mode of
如果在语言模型的特定模式下存在，那会出错
if it's there in the specific mode of the language model what can go wrong
the language model what can go wrong with family
和家人一起
这样我们就可以在训练句子中说出您缺少的句子
the language model what can go wrong with family
so that we would say in the training sentences which is missing would you
这样我们就可以在训练句子中说出您缺少的句子
sentences which is missing would you ever be able to predict that work no
曾经能够预测这项工作不好，所以显然有很多
ever be able to predict that work no okay so obviously there are lots of
okay so obviously there are lots of tricks you can go about this all right
您可以解决这个问题的技巧，它们使用不同的名称，但我
tricks you can go about this all right and they go with different names but I'm
and they go with different names but I'm gonna show you briefly on how we can do
我将向您简要介绍如何实现2000万人口的目标，但让我
gonna show you briefly on how we can do a 20 million population but let me just
a 20 million population but let me just put all of these things up here in the
将所有这些东西放在这里，您在我们估算的时候
put all of these things up here in the estimation you in the when we estimated
estimation you in the when we estimated this parameter say we defined basically
这个参数说我们基本上将MLE估计定义为n JK / MJ in
this parameter say we defined basically the MLE estimate as being n JK / MJ in
the MLE estimate as being n JK / MJ in science basically the transitions from J
科学基本上是从J到其他任何东西的过渡，当您总结
science basically the transitions from J to anything else and when you sum the
to anything else and when you sum the mjk whole case you get we do know this
mjk整个案例，您知道我们确实很抱歉，因此有一种解决方法
mjk whole case you get we do know this as n sorry right so a way to fix
as n sorry right so a way to fix whatever problems you have with Emily is
艾米丽（Emily）遇到的任何问题都无关紧要
whatever problems you have with Emily is irrelevant
irrelevant taking the Emily estimate for a JK use
用Jmi的Emily估算值使用您的加权平均值
taking the Emily estimate for a JK use some weighted average of what you
some weighted average of what you completely with Emily and also the K
完全与Emily以及事物NK除以L的K一起在这里
completely with Emily and also the K where things NK divided by L so here
where things NK divided by L so here we're interested in the transitions from
我们对Zeta K的过渡很感兴趣，但是这个词是做什么的
we're interested in the transitions from Zeta K but this term does what it
Zeta K but this term does what it accounts for many times I see the word
占了很多次，我看到蛋糕这个词不是很在乎
accounts for many times I see the word cake it doesn't really care about
cake it doesn't really care about transitions
过渡好吧，这是您选择亚特兰大的地方
transitions okay so and this is you select Atlanta
okay so and this is you select Atlanta cross validation so this is not Bayesian
交叉验证，所以这不是贝叶斯算法，我们将看到我们如何可能获得
cross validation so this is not Bayesian we will see how possibly we can get
we will see how possibly we can get something like that with a basin
像这样的盆地配方好了，所以这叫做
something like that with a basin formulation okay so this is called the
formulation okay so this is called the style version is called the belt
样式版本称为皮带平滑，任何人服用
style version is called the belt smoothing okay where anyone taking the
smoothing okay where anyone taking the MLE estimate we take a weighted average
MLE估计我们对Emily估计或对角线进行加权平均
MLE estimate we take a weighted average of the Emily estimate or diagonally
of the Emily estimate or diagonally consists and also lambda times of cake
包括蛋糕的lambda时间，这是频率的单位
consists and also lambda times of cake where this is the unit of frequencies
where this is the unit of frequencies which is NK / yeah all right so let's
是NK /是的，所以让我们来看看如何获​​得测量模型
which is NK / yeah all right so let's take how we get the measure model for
take how we get the measure model for this let me put all of this thing up
这让我把所有这些东西都放起来了，实际上这很简单，但是假设
this let me put all of this thing up actually this is very simple but assumes
actually this is very simple but assumes that you know something about different
您会像以前一样了解不同的分布，所以这是
that you know something about different distributions as prior so this is the
distributions as prior so this is the situation and this is the matrix a that
情况，这是矩阵a，我的所有观察都在搅动它
situation and this is the matrix a that is being stirred by all my observations
is being stirred by all my observations so that's why you see these links like
所以这就是为什么您看到这些链接，而每个链接都是第一个
so that's why you see these links like that and each of this is the first in
that and each of this is the first in the a matrix so if you think this will
这个矩阵，所以如果您认为这将给我过渡的可能性
the a matrix so if you think this will give me the probabilities to transition
give me the probabilities to transition from one to state to state one from one
从一状态到一状态从一到清从一二三一二
from one to state to state one from one to clear from one two three one two
to clear from one two three one two three etc so the sum of these things is
三个等等，所以这些东西的总和等于1好
three etc so the sum of these things is equal to 1 okay
equal to 1 okay so then this will give you the
因此，这将为您提供从已知的过渡-好的
so then this will give you the transition from you know the one - okay
transition from you know the one - okay and so I'm going to take the pitch of
因此，我将采用这种玫瑰紫水晶的音调，然后
and so I'm going to take the pitch of this Rose amethyst and then I'm going to
this Rose amethyst and then I'm going to do is I am going to put a on each of
我要做的是将这些行的每一行都放好，这一行将
do is I am going to put a on each of these rows okay and this one is going to
these rows okay and this one is going to be the declare distribution that looks
是看起来您在此处看到距离的方式的声明分布
be the declare distribution that looks the way that you see here the distance
the way that you see here the distance basically from silty clay have been
基本上是用粉质黏土写的有趣的方式
basically from silty clay have been written in an interesting way where I
written in an interesting way where I have the time you know it's not from the
有时间知道不是细节，基本上是0
have the time you know it's not from the details but basically a 0 comes
details but basically a 0 comes everywhere then I have M 0 2 and carry
到处都有M 0 2并携带，所以这是如果您可以取平均值的话
everywhere then I have M 0 2 and carry so this is if you can take the mean of
so this is if you can take the mean of this declare distribution the mean comes
此声明分布的平均值为N ok，其强度为
this declare distribution the mean comes to the N ok and the strength of which is
to the N ok and the strength of which is defined by this coefficient of 0 okay so
由这个系数定义为0还可以
defined by this coefficient of 0 okay so so
let's see what this is going to do some of these min satisfies the stomach
我将把它强加在捆绑包上，所以让我们看看这将做些什么
这些最小的满足胃套必须煮好一个，所以
let's see what this is going to do some of these min satisfies the stomach
of these min satisfies the stomach encase has to be cooked one alright so
这些最小的满足胃套必须煮好一个，所以
encase has to be cooked one alright so this is the prior and I claim that the
这是先验的，我声称对于它的后验，你知道我可以说，
this is the prior and I claim that the posterior for its you know I can say and
posterior for its you know I can say and I remind you it's a healthy purge a
我提醒您，这是健康的清除方法，其中包含过渡概率
I remind you it's a healthy purge a contains the transition probabilities
contains the transition probabilities from J to 1 to J 2 to 20 to 3 right all
从J到1到J 2到20到3对所有你知道的教育
from J to 1 to J 2 to 20 to 3 right all of the things education you know this
of the things education you know this chest do you remember what time he has
你记得他什么时候去看他的分析书吗？
chest do you remember what time he has so he can look at the analytical
so he can look at the analytical expression which a for alpha J 1 so the
表达式，其中a表示alpha J 1，因此J 1的终点将是和
expression which a for alpha J 1 so the terminal for J 1 is going to be sum
terminal for J 1 is going to be sum alpha G want some power what's the power
阿尔法G需要一些力量什么是力量
你们对青年的计算机功能我们有一个分布，它看起来
terminal for J 1 is going to be sum alpha G want some power what's the power
you guys to the computer power of youth we have a distribution of does it look
你们对青年的计算机功能我们有一个分布，它看起来
we have a distribution of does it look like you can take for distribution some
就像您可以分配一些参数theta 1 theta 2等等
like you can take for distribution some parameters theta 1 theta 2 etc you're
parameters theta 1 theta 2 etc you're going to have people line to what power
要让人们了解什么力量
-这-天鹅和神话般的，如果他们来到这个力量减去1对
parameters theta 1 theta 2 etc you're going to have people line to what power
- this - swan and mythic a it would be if they came to this power minus 1 right
-这-天鹅和神话般的，如果他们来到这个力量减去1对
if they came to this power minus 1 right can you suppress with the likelihood
您能否以与我们具有相同形式的可能性来压制
can you suppress with the likelihood that had the same form that we had
that had the same form that we had before that they were the parameters to
在此之前，它们是某种力量的参数，您还记得我的可能性
before that they were the parameters to some power you remember the likelihood I
some power you remember the likelihood I don't want to go back 20 slides all
不想回去20张幻灯片好了
don't want to go back 20 slides all right
你记得
you remember
因此，您现在可以看到声明分配的权利是适当的
so you can see now the right to declare distribution is the appropriate
distribution is the appropriate conjugate prior alright so you multiply
共轭先验好吧，所以你在这里将失速倍增，我会说一些力量
conjugate prior alright so you multiply stall here with I'd say to some power
stall here with I'd say to some power and here with a educate some power and
在这里教育一些力量，小写和反对这将给你
and here with a educate some power and lower case and object this will give you
lower case and object this will give you a very clear prior base okay so the
一个非常明确的先验基础还可以，所以当天的协作液是
a very clear prior base okay so the event of the day the collab liquid is
event of the day the collab liquid is declared distribution if the priors in
如果先验在酒后分配，则宣布分配
declared distribution if the priors in the liquor distribution the posterior
the liquor distribution the posterior will come to be a digital distribution
将成为一个数字分布，后验我们有相同的
will come to be a digital distribution and the posterior we have the same
and the posterior we have the same promise the prior with updated
保证具有更新参数的先验，这将是
promise the prior with updated parameters and this will be the form of
parameters and this will be the form of the the operator will be the
该运算符将是参数为零的分布
the the operator will be the distribution with parameters of a zero
distribution with parameters of a zero times M the comes from the prior NJ not
M是来自先前NJ而不是标量，而Jerry NJ是向量的向量
times M the comes from the prior NJ not the scalar and Jerry NJ is the vector of
the scalar and Jerry NJ is the vector of the time to transition from TJ to state
从TJ过渡到状态一的时间，从状态a过渡到状态2，从NJ过渡到状态一的时间
the time to transition from TJ to state one from state a to state two and NJ to
one from state a to state two and NJ to take care okay
保重好吧，所以后验分布看起来是
take care okay so the posterior distribution looks it's
so the posterior distribution looks it's not going close from the way that this
距离这基本上不是一个更好的方式
not going close from the way that this is this basically to do a better
is this basically to do a better estimation and prediction for the
语言模型的估计和预测是一回事，
estimation and prediction for the language model that's one thing and
language model that's one thing and secondly how do you actually can go and
其次，您实际上如何去问您有关0名称的问题
secondly how do you actually can go and ask you something about that for 0 name
ask you something about that for 0 name okay so how do you find this parameter
好的，那么您如何找到先前看到的此参数，但请确保
okay so how do you find this parameter seen in the prior but make sure
我们减少声望仍然是JK，所以每个都是
we reduce the prestige remain a JK so each of this is that the declared
each of this is that the declared distribution we're going to use the
分布，我们将使用后验最小值和后验均值
distribution we're going to use the posterior min and the posterior mean
posterior min and the posterior mean basically for the this distribution if
基本上，对于这种分布，如果您将每个分区都设为K
basically for the this distribution if you take each of the partitions the K
you take each of the partitions the K partition it will be M say k plus alpha
分区是M说k加alpha 0 MK / MJ假设晚餐，好的，所以
partition it will be M say k plus alpha 0 MK / MJ suppose dinner and okay so
0 MK / MJ suppose dinner and okay so into the trade is the frequency of
进入交易的频率是从J到K乘以n J的频率，这是
into the trade is the frequency of transition from J to K times n J this is
transition from J to K times n J this is what we came with family estimation plus
我们得出的家庭估计数加上1加0乘以MK和J加上alpha 0和
what we came with family estimation plus 1 plus 0 times MK and J plus alpha 0 and
1 plus 0 times MK and J plus alpha 0 and I can write this expression like this
我可以像这样为lambda J编写这样的表达式：alpha 0 / MJ plus alpha
I can write this expression like this for lambda J is alpha 0 / MJ plus alpha
for lambda J is alpha 0 / MJ plus alpha 0 so basically this approximation that
0基本上就是这个近似值，人们在出现之前就已经介绍过了
0 so basically this approximation that people introduced before it comes out to
people introduced before it comes out to be actually the posterior min when it
当它在滚动时使用非常清晰的先验时，实际上是后验分钟
be actually the posterior min when it uses very clear prior on the rolls of
uses very clear prior on the rolls of the transition matrix a JK okay so the
过渡矩阵一个JK好吧，所以第一个晚上因为0
the transition matrix a JK okay so the first evening because the 0 the
first evening because the 0 the procedure mean really is the transition
过程均值实际上是从状态a到状态K的转变概率
procedure mean really is the transition probability from state a to state K ok
probability from state a to state K ok so this integration it is defined
因此，此集成是专门根据先验条件定义的
so this integration it is defined exclusively in terms of the prior
exclusively in terms of the prior strength of for 0 and also the number of
强度为0，以及她在
strength of for 0 and also the number of time she worked on on stage a on the
time she worked on on stage a on the word shape
字形
好的，所以问题是代表所有先驱者都可以，这不是
time she worked on on stage a on the word shape
okay so the question is rep all pioneers going to be okay and that is not a
好的，所以问题是代表所有先驱者都可以，这不是
going to be okay and that is not a trivial problem so I'm going to if it's
琐碎的问题，所以我要去了解一下它是否可能以某种方式知道
trivial problem so I'm going to if it's something that I know it somehow might
something that I know it somehow might slide in the okay it comes to be the
没关系，一天结束时还是一样
slide in the okay it comes to be the same thing at the end of the day the
same thing at the end of the day the likelihood alright remember the steps we
好吧，还记得我们假设每个孔独立于
likelihood alright remember the steps we assume that each hole is independent of
assume that each hole is independent of each other so the likelihood basically
彼此，所以可能性基本上是该所有行的乘积
each other so the likelihood basically is the product of all the rows of this
is the product of all the rows of this interesting relationship potential
有趣的关系潜力应该有人从哪里传播
interesting relationship potential should somebody transmit from where this
should somebody transmit from where this is coming I were very happy
快来了，我感到非常高兴
所以请记住我们乘以好，然后乘以，然后得到后验
should somebody transmit from where this is coming I were very happy
so remember we multiply all right we multiply and then we got a posterior
所以请记住我们乘以好，然后乘以，然后得到后验
multiply and then we got a posterior that he was also at the clear
他也很清楚地分布，而这家银行的确是
that he was also at the clear distribution and this Bank was really an
distribution and this Bank was really an j plus alpha so did this formula come
j加alpha，所以这个公式来了
声明分布，我们先与dirichlet相乘，然后设置
distribution and this Bank was really an j plus alpha so did this formula come
declare distribution we multiply with the dirichlet prior and then we set the
声明分布，我们先与dirichlet相乘，然后设置
the dirichlet prior and then we set the reason the posterior is a data flow
后验也是数据流分布的原因，所以我可以告诉
reason the posterior is a data flow distribution as well so this I can tell
distribution as well so this I can tell you it reminds me very much the
你让我很想起延迟的归一化因素
you it reminds me very much the normalizing factor of the delay
normalizing factor of the delay distribution she wanted to have 1 over
她希望在Aquacade上拥有1个发行版，这确实是
distribution she wanted to have 1 over the Aquacade this is really the
the Aquacade this is really the normalizing question of what
关于什么分布问题的归一化问题记得我们有
normalizing question of what distributional problem remember we have
distributional problem remember we have the likelihood we assimilate a prior
在本术语中，我们吸收了先于精神主导的可能性，因此
the likelihood we assimilate a prior than spirit-led so for this term in the
than spirit-led so for this term in the denominator came from
分母来自
这是先生的归一化因素。主教
than spirit-led so for this term in the denominator came from
that's the normalizing factor with mr. Bishop
所以这是在先权利的归一化因素，要对其进行归一化
so it's the normalizing factor of the prior right and to normalize it you have
prior right and to normalize it you have to multiply and divide by this factor so
乘以除以这个因子，因此无论您拥有什么，我们都是最好的时光之一
to multiply and divide by this factor so one of our best times whatever you have
one of our best times whatever you have as a problem will give you a declared
因为一个问题将给你一个声明的后验，这将是
as a problem will give you a declared posterior and this would be the
posterior and this would be the normalization factor to the power so the
幂的归一化因子，因此乘积超过父亲，并且
normalization factor to the power so the product over J a father and also the
product over J a father and also the transition matrix of this ratio will
这个比率的转换矩阵基本上会给您明确的
transition matrix of this ratio will basically give you explicitly the
basically give you explicitly the marginal likelihood and what you can do
边际可能性，您可以做的是，如果您有兴趣现在
marginal likelihood and what you can do is if you are interested to actually now
is if you are interested to actually now go and compute this parameters for
去计算这个参数，例如，您知道您能做的就是
go and compute this parameters for example you know what you can do is you
example you know what you can do is you can do an optimization problem and you
可以做一个优化问题，您可以找到实际的计算半值
can do an optimization problem and you can find the actual calculations semi
can find the actual calculations semi analytically basically this paper by
从理论上讲，Mincha的这篇论文基本上使用此表达式进行计算
analytically basically this paper by Mincha using this expression to compute
Mincha using this expression to compute these parameters to this expression the
这些参数表达后，我们的政治过渡就来了
these parameters to this expression the posterior comes our political transition
posterior comes our political transition matrix to be declared distribution so
要声明分布的矩阵，因此从J到K的跃迁具有此均值
matrix to be declared distribution so the transition from J to K has this mean
the transition from J to K has this mean value and this mean value is the
值，该平均值基本上是
value and this mean value is the weighted average basically of the
weighted average basically of the diagram frequencies to collide and this
图中的频率发生碰撞，并且该模板与先前的
diagram frequencies to collide and this template that has to do with the prior
template that has to do with the prior now I remind you but if you do this
现在我提醒您，但是如果您凭经验这样做，人们会接受
now I remind you but if you do this empirically people will take this
empirically people will take this coefficient MK to be how many times you
系数MK等于您拥有数据搜索世界的次数
coefficient MK to be how many times you have the world carrying the data search
have the world carrying the data search alright so here's X ability because NK
好吧，这里是X的能力，因为NK是根据先验定义的，所以
alright so here's X ability because NK is defined in terms of the prior so the
is defined in terms of the prior so the question is what do you take as MK so
问题是，您如何看待MK？
保存下来的任何东西都在这里看这个方程式，它使
is defined in terms of the prior so the question is what do you take as MK so
anything what it saved look at this equation here and it makes
保存下来的任何东西都在这里看这个方程式，它使
look at this equation here and it makes an K is proportional today such that and
今天K与K成正比，所以JK大于零，你能告诉我吗
an K is proportional today such that and JK greater than zero can you tell me
JK greater than zero can you tell me what this change
朝着什么样的方向迈进，我们注意到了什么
what this change towards take us m'kay what noticing all
towards take us m'kay what noticing all the times you see the words a what how
您看到单词的次数a您转换到网络K的次数是多少
the times you see the words a what how many times you transition to the web K
many times you transition to the web K for many other words a okay because in
换句话说，还可以，因为从本质上讲，这是我拥有的熵，
for many other words a okay because in essence this is an entropy I have and
essence this is an entropy I have and how many times you say given war okay
您说多少次战争还可以，孟菲斯UNC就有一个例子
how many times you say given war okay and there is an example in Memphis UNC
and there is an example in Memphis UNC okay and you know this that always comes
好吧，你知道这总是在你之后
okay and you know this that always comes after you
after you so if you need to find the transition
因此，如果您需要找到过渡概率，基本上可以给
so if you need to find the transition probabilities basically can give the
probabilities basically can give the same thing and see something you know
同样的事情，看到你知道的天才出现，来复习一下，
same thing and see something you know genius comes up to review all right and
genius comes up to review all right and you will notice the times that you see
您会注意到在该模型中看到的时间是关于
you will notice the times that you see appear in this model it's about the
appear in this model it's about the thing okay eleven times is the same but
十一次没事是一样的，但是您可以利用利用语言
thing okay eleven times is the same but utilizations language you just you could
utilizations language you just you could let you etcetera you know see you
让您等一下，您知道除了此模型外，您看到的一切
let you etcetera you know see you whatever but in this model into account
whatever but in this model into account that this transition probability is the
该过渡概率是这些随机变量的加权平均值
that this transition probability is the weighted average of these random
weighted average of these random frequencies and how many times you
频率以及您转换到由定义的单词ok的次数
frequencies and how many times you transition to the word k okay defined by
transition to the word k okay defined by this definition does this model performs
这个定义是否可以更好地找到其他任何种类的模型
this definition does this model performs way better found the any other sort of
way better found the any other sort of known estimate for for m'kay if I
如果我了解m'kay的已知估算值，基本上是非
known estimate for for m'kay if I understand is the basically non
understand is the basically non parametric model and usually this non
参数模型，通常这种非参数模型使用实用
parametric model and usually this non parametric models use practical
parametric models use practical techniques so you can think you know
技术，因此您可以认为自己知道，因为您对模型建模感兴趣
techniques so you can think you know since you are interested in model the
since you are interested in model the transition from one world to another
从一个世界过渡到另一个世界，这次您可以想到
transition from one world to another this you can think of this this time so
this you can think of this this time so you can use ideas from sequence to
您可以使用从顺序到蒙特卡洛的想法来做到这一点
you can use ideas from sequence to Montecarlo to do that
Montecarlo to do that into service no parametric methods but I
没有参数化方法投入使用，但我知道通过减少，我可以回到这里
into service no parametric methods but I know by reducing I can go back here I
know by reducing I can go back here I have I'm using the declared distribution
我是否在使用已声明的分发作为先例之前知道了它的内容
have I'm using the declared distribution as a prior their prior you know what it
as a prior their prior you know what it is that they reflect process and I don't
是他们反映了过程，我不知道您会从中获利
is that they reflect process and I don't know kind of you will do a profit from
know kind of you will do a profit from this what's the difference not
这不是自动的区别，但是如果我从这里去
this what's the difference not automatically but if I go from this
automatically but if I go from this distribution to the clip process what
向剪辑过程分发您所知道的一般过程
distribution to the clip process what you know what did the process in general
you know what did the process in general will allow me to do that this particular
可以让我做到这一点，这种特殊的模式将不允许任何人知道
will allow me to do that this particular model would not allow me anybody knows
所以在这种情况下，我有从J到状态0到K的转换
so in this case right I have transitions from J to state 0 to K right in
from J to state 0 to K right in different postures I'm gonna be able to
我将能够使用不同的姿势来处理状态
different postures I'm gonna be able to have transitions to handle states
安东尼好吧，这样一来，最糟糕的人就没有在会计师那里见过
Antony okay so that way worst of you have not seen with the accountant in the
have not seen with the accountant in the private market you know because you have
你知道的私人市场，因为你可以过渡到所有的东西，但是我已经
private market you know because you have transitions to everything okay but I've
transitions to everything okay but I've now told it will not allow you to do
现在告诉它不允许您这样做，所以raclette过程是您知道的
now told it will not allow you to do this so the raclette process is you know
this so the raclette process is you know that's why we call it a non parametric
这就是为什么我们称其为非参数模型，因为您实际上拥有
that's why we call it a non parametric model because effectively you have
model because effectively you have infinite parameters to define this model
无限参数定义此模型，因此，如果您对实际
infinite parameters to define this model so if you are interested the actually
so if you are interested the actually the world of tech from Oxford basically
牛津大学的技术世界基本上就是其中之一
the world of tech from Oxford basically is the one that has produced one of the
is the one that has produced one of the best language models basically using the
最佳语言模型，基本上是先使用修复过程
best language models basically using the repair process priors from doing that
我在这里提到了其他一些系数为1 1 1 1的东西，你知道吗
I mentioned something else here with coefficients 1 1 1 1 the you know what
coefficients 1 1 1 1 the you know what is going to happen at the end of the day
将会在这一天结束时发生，因为每个人
is going to happen at the end of the day on this estimate because that everybody
on this estimate because that everybody does and the girls you know it is your
确实和你知道的女孩是你的系列，以经验写成
does and the girls you know it is your series empirically written in a lots of
series empirically written in a lots of machine learning books so the estimate
机器学习书籍，所以估计AJ Clary是m JK / MJ，所以如果我的数据
machine learning books so the estimate AJ Clary was m JK / MJ so if my data
AJ Clary was m JK / MJ so if my data layer has coefficients 1 1 1 1 ok all
层的系数为1 1 1 1好的，这实际上是这件事要做的
layer has coefficients 1 1 1 1 ok all was what actually this thing is going to
was what actually this thing is going to come to be what is this what will happen
变成这是什么，数字先验的平均值将发生什么
come to be what is this what will happen to the mean of digital prior with
to the mean of digital prior with Kristin's want
克里斯汀的需求
所以会得出这个报价在这里是1，这将是1
to the mean of digital prior with Kristin's want
so it will come out that this quotation here would be 1 and this would be 1
所以会得出这个报价在这里是1，这将是1
here would be 1 and this would be 1 subjectively what you will be doing in
从主观上讲，您将在计算后验时将要做什么
subjectively what you will be doing in computing the posterior mean you will be
computing the posterior mean you will be adding the quantity 1 all the empirical
将所有经验牛的数量加1
adding the quantity 1 all the empirical cows
cows so if one word for example doesn't exist
因此，例如，如果训练数据集中不存在一个词，那么您将
so if one word for example doesn't exist a term in the training data set you will
a term in the training data set you will get 1 there so the transition from J to
在那得到1，所以从J到那个的过渡不会是0，你不会
get 1 there so the transition from J to that one will not be 0 you're not gonna
that one will not be 0 you're not gonna get anything worth it because the
得到任何值得的东西，因为先前的组织通常会
get anything worth it because the organization that prior will usually
organization that prior will usually have a transition to an award
可以过渡到奖项了，这张图让我看到了
have a transition to an award okay and this graph would let me see
okay and this graph would let me see what the name is and plus 1 or something
名称是什么，加上1或什么是非常典型的
what the name is and plus 1 or something this is very typical
我记得很好的地方和我在一起，所以这是令人愉快的，所以
somewhere I remember well is with me okay so this is the mouthing okay so
okay so this is the mouthing okay so here we have an evolution of the space
在这里，我们对空间进行了演变，就像您在这里看到的那样，这些是我的
here we have an evolution of the space the way that you see here these are my
the way that you see here these are my exist this or the observations they have
存在这个或他们所拥有的观察，并且您知道引入的目的
exist this or the observations they have and you know the purpose of introducing
and you know the purpose of introducing sort of this length and representations
这种长度和表示形式之类的原因是，它使我们能够
sort of this length and representations is because it allows us to take very
is because it allows us to take very complex dependencies between the
外部之间的复杂依赖关系还可以，即使给定
complex dependencies between the external okay so even though given let's
external okay so even though given let's say this this observation and
说这个观察和观察是彼此独立的
say this this observation and observation are independent of each
observation are independent of each other by integrator resist how okay
集成商提供的其他服务可抵御lexis相互依赖的方式，所以这是一个
other by integrator resist how okay lexis depend on each other so this is a
lexis depend on each other so this is a much more complicated model than the
即使以条件为条件，模型也比马尔可夫模型复杂得多
much more complicated model than the Markov model even though conditioned on
Markov model even though conditioned on Z you have conditioned you know this GI
Z您已经调理过，就知道这种GI独立性关系简化了
Z you have conditioned you know this GI independence relations that simplify the
independence relations that simplify the problem okay so let me just write the
问题好吧，所以我只写概率分布
problem okay so let me just write the probability distribution is going to
probability distribution is going to look like the joint of action three okay
看起来像是动作三的联合，再次是处于
look like the joint of action three okay is again the probability of being in
is again the probability of being in state C 1 we have the transition
在状态C 1中，我们具有与马尔可夫一样的转移概率
state C 1 we have the transition probability exactly as in the markov
probability exactly as in the markov model and then we have the observation
模型，然后我们有观测概率，所以此时
model and then we have the observation probabilities so at this time the
probabilities so at this time the probability of X and given Zn sorry hmm
X的概率和给定的Zn对不起hmm模型
probability of X and given Zn sorry hmm model
model we will take the state Z to be discreet
我们将状态Z谨慎对待，但观察性可以是任何东西
we will take the state Z to be discreet but the observation sex can be anything
but the observation sex can be anything you want to so it can be - them can be
你想这样-他们可以多不，我可以是任何一种
you want to so it can be - them can be multi no me can be any sort of
multi no me can be any sort of distribution if you make this have this
分布，如果您将此位置设为高斯，则将其设为
distribution if you make this have this position to be Gaussian and this to be a
position to be Gaussian and this to be a Gaussian then you get in here
高斯，那么您基本上可以在这里进入高斯模型，我们将
Gaussian then you get in here Gaussian models basically that we will
Gaussian models basically that we will see later on and from there if you can
稍后再查看，是否可以得到类似于卡尔曼滤波的一年
see later on and from there if you can get a year similar to Kalman filtering
get a year similar to Kalman filtering but right now we're going to take that
但是现在我们要考虑的是，这是一个离散分布
but right now we're going to take that this is a discrete distribution this can
this is a discrete distribution this can be we leave it on the earth so it can be
是因为我们将其留在地球上，所以它可以是我们想要的任何东西，我们希望可以
be we leave it on the earth so it can be anything we want we want to alright
非常类似于高斯混合模型
so extremely similar to a Gaussian mixture model okay
mixture model okay the only difference so imagine that we
唯一的区别是，想象一下，我们在
the only difference so imagine that we have this liquid distance right of the
have this liquid distance right of the mixture quotations that tells you when
混合引语告诉您何时知道，所以我们说一下
mixture quotations that tells you when you know so let's say the parameter of
you know so let's say the parameter of XT given the state is a Gaussian all
XT给定状态是高斯状态，也许在我们的混合模型中，
XT given the state is a Gaussian all right and maybe in our mixture model we
right and maybe in our mixture model we have three different gaussian right so k
有三个不同的高斯权，所以k等于1 2或3
have three different gaussian right so k equal 1 2 or 3
equal 1 2 or 3 so if your sister is a data set that
因此，如果您的姐姐是来自三个不同高斯的数据集就可以了
so if your sister is a data set that comes from three different gaussian okay
comes from three different gaussian okay but incident models is a little more
但是事件模型稍微复杂一点，因为z1和z2会再次出现
but incident models is a little more complicated because z1 and z2 will again
complicated because z1 and z2 will again point to the childís Gaussian but won't
指向孩子的高斯，但不会和三个孩子一起生存，你知道
point to the childís Gaussian but won't survive with three you know what the
survive with three you know what the state trip is gonna be on this ride the
这次国家旅行将在高斯上进行，因此您开始采样
state trip is gonna be on this ride the Gaussian so you start taking samples
Gaussian so you start taking samples from this until all so why have you find
从这直到所有，所以为什么要在这个高斯身上找到自己，那是什么
from this until all so why have you find yourself on this Gaussian so what's the
yourself on this Gaussian so what's the difference of this from a Gaussian
与高斯混合的区别区别很简单
difference of this from a Gaussian mixture the difference is very simple
mixture the difference is very simple that the state are basically now a
如果您接下来采样，该状态基本上就是马尔可夫链，这取决于
that the state are basically now a Markov chain if you sample next depends
Markov chain if you sample next depends what state they were before all right so
他们没事之前处于什么状态，所以在很多方面这都类似于
what state they were before all right so in many ways this is very similar to a
in many ways this is very similar to a diversion mixed model behind
转移混合模型后面没有这个我可以连接
diversion mixed model behind without this all right I connected
without this all right I connected through the Markovian property basically
通过马尔可夫属性，您基本上可以知道
through the Markovian property basically you know the transition of the
you know the transition of the permeability of GI from given CI - Juan
给定CI的GI渗透率-Juan你在这里看到的是
permeability of GI from given CI - Juan what you see here is in constraints on
what you see here is in constraints on how we go from you know from one state
我们如何从您所知从一种状态过渡到另一种状态
how we go from you know from one state to another
to another can you tell me if I want to generate
您能告诉我是否要在给定历史时间的情况下生成此数据吗？
can you tell me if I want to generate this data given historical time for this
this data given historical time for this distribution can somebody give me an
如果我想停止生成，发行人可以给我一个主意
distribution can somebody give me an idea if I want to to stop generating
idea if I want to to stop generating this picture here and it's this
这是这张图片，这是适度的观察方向
this picture here and it's this observation modest is a direction with
observation modest is a direction with its own mean and variance how are you
它自己的均值和方差您将如何生成图片
its own mean and variance how are you going to generate the picture looking at
going to generate the picture looking at this distribution
这种分布不安，我会看起来像
this distribution what's restless I'm going to look like
what's restless I'm going to look like to generate data the way that you seen
以您看到图片的方式生成数据，那么您怎么样
to generate data the way that you seen the showing the picture so how are you
the showing the picture so how are you going to generate the observations that
将产生我们从高斯那里看到的观测结果，您可以看到
going to generate the observations that we saw there from gaussians you can see
we saw there from gaussians you can see here so what do we do what's the first
在这里，我们该怎么做？第一步
here so what do we do what's the first step
从g1的这种分布开始的初始状态
from this distribution of g1 the initial State
State alright I got it what's next alright the
好吧，我知道了，下一步是好吧，下一步是我们可以对实际样本进行采样吗
alright I got it what's next alright the next thing is can we sample actual right
next thing is can we sample actual right the answer is yes we can sell furniture
答案是肯定的，我们可以根据给定的价格出售家具d --- rom
the answer is yes we can sell furniture on the given is d---rom from this
on the given is d---rom from this probability okay what's next
概率好吧接下来我们有一个零样本，现在
probability okay what's next we have a sample of zero and now also
we have a sample of zero and now also given the sample whatever we gonna do
给样品我们要做的一切，现在给我们三个
given the sample whatever we gonna do samples it to now giving us the three we
samples it to now giving us the three we can sample it do etc so mister you get
可以取样做等，所以先生，您会得到这张图片，您会在左侧看到
can sample it do etc so mister you get this picture that you see on the left
this picture that you see on the left okay so it is a very exactly like a
好吧，所以它非常像高斯混合，唯一的区别是
okay so it is a very exactly like a Gaussian mixture the only difference is
Gaussian mixture the only difference is in a Gaussian mixture you don't have
在高斯混合中，您没有这种过渡概率，我们
in a Gaussian mixture you don't have this transition probability which we
this transition probability which we have here okay because we're running out
在这里还可以，因为如果我不能撒尿，我们的时间就不多了
have here okay because we're running out of time if I can't pee
不，我看不到，我现在必须要利用你的想象力，因为
nope I don't see it I'm gonna have to I have to use your imagination now because
have to use your imagination now because who knows what try this now okay
谁知道现在尝试这个好吗
我可以写出C 1的初始概率，因为最终
have to use your imagination now because who knows what try this now okay
it was made that I can write the initial probability of C 1 because eventually
我可以写出C 1的初始概率，因为最终
probability of C 1 because eventually we're going to be interesting to do
我们将很有趣地在此进行参数的影响
we're going to be interesting to do influence of the parameters in this
influence of the parameters in this distribution I can write it like that
分布，我可以这样写，这样你就可以做些什么
distribution I can write it like that so you can do something exactly what
so you can do something exactly what this equation gives me on the bottom so
这个方程式使我处于最底层，所以我在这里假设状态D 1为
this equation gives me on the bottom so I'm assuming here that the states D 1 is
I'm assuming here that the states D 1 is discrete fixed K stage so that is PI K
离散的固定K级，因此为PI K
是说我在什么状态还可以，在哪里的概率
I'm assuming here that the states D 1 is discrete fixed K stage so that is PI K
is the probability that that would say one I am on what state okay and where is
是说我在什么状态还可以，在哪里的概率
one I am on what state okay and where is this coming because this discrete
这是因为这个离散变量Z aleni
this coming because this discrete variable Z the aleni
所以当ZK等于RI的时候我会赢得欢呼的，意思是我说第一个
so I'm gonna get okay cheer win when Z K is equal to R I mean I say the first
is equal to R I mean I say the first risk video I should not have it here but
冒险视频，我不应该在这里放，但是哦，嘿，第32节实际上没有
risk video I should not have it here but oh hey the first verse 32 no actually
oh hey the first verse 32 no actually you know what
你知道这不应该是我应该什么
you know what this should not be an i what should this
this should not be an i what should this be right so when the state you know I'm
是正确的，所以当您知道状态为0时，这里就是一个数据集
be right so when the state you know I'm one dataset here right when 0 C is from
one dataset here right when 0 C is from state that's a notation like this what's
表示这样的符号新的1 K等于1好，所以当z1 k
state that's a notation like this what's new 1 K is equal to 1 okay so when z1 k
new 1 K is equal to 1 okay so when z1 k equal to 1 this will give me DK and all
等于1，这将给我DK，而所有其他项的指数为0，所以
equal to 1 this will give me DK and all the other terms we have an exponent 0 so
the other terms we have an exponent 0 so would be equal to 1 so I get basically
等于1，所以我得到的距离基本上等于PI K
would be equal to 1 so I get basically the distance equal to PI K all right
the distance equal to PI K all right does this make sense
这有意义吗
好吧，这基本上就是我们对于马尔可夫链所拥有的，所以
the distance equal to PI K all right does this make sense
alright this exactly basically what we had for the Markov chain right so
好吧，这基本上就是我们对于马尔可夫链所拥有的，所以
had for the Markov chain right so there's nothing different this is the
没什么不同，这是从J到K和kk中的J的过渡
there's nothing different this is the transition from J to K and J in k k
transition from J to K and J in k k dimensional right they can take K States
他们可以采取K国的维权，并根据经验来实现这一目标
dimensional right they can take K States and on the experiences to make this
and on the experiences to make this explicit if I have GN minus 1 J this is
如果我有GN减1 J，则明确表示，当N减1状态为时，此值等于1
explicit if I have GN minus 1 J this is equal to 1 when the N minus 1 state is
equal to 1 when the N minus 1 state is on J status and this one a time step
关于J状态，这是一个时间步，那么我很好，所以如果这是
on J status and this one a time step then I'm alakay alright so if this is
then I'm alakay alright so if this is the case the exponents equal to 1 and
指数等于1的情况，这给了我一个JK，其余的给我的是
the case the exponents equal to 1 and this give me a JK the rest gives me is
this give me a JK the rest gives me is doing exponent so I get a contribution
做指数，所以我得到1的贡献，所以没有变化
doing exponent so I get a contribution of 1 so nothing changes
of 1 so nothing changes ok so here's what we're interested we're
好吧，这就是我们感兴趣的，我们感兴趣的是为隐藏的物体质子化
ok so here's what we're interested we're interested to protonate for the hidden
interested to protonate for the hidden market one of the dispositions and also
市场配置之一，也是历史概率pi K势
market one of the dispositions and also the history probabilities pi K potential
the history probabilities pi K potential and if you're introducing observation
如果您要介绍观察，请爱他们，这个观察模型我们
and if you're introducing observation love them and this observation model we
love them and this observation model we have the chain parameters and we need to
有链参数，我们也需要计算它，好吧，你知道我们
have the chain parameters and we need to compute this as well ok and you know we
compute this as well ok and you know we can consider several different choices
可以考虑几种不同的选择，这对于幻灯片来说是致命的，但是您可以
can consider several different choices it's lethal for the slides but you can
it's lethal for the slides but you can imagine if you are on state K let's say
想像一下，如果您处于状态K，那么如果这个系数可以是PKA且
imagine if you are on state K let's say then if this coefficients can be PKA and
then if this coefficients can be PKA and this will be the chosen correspondent
这将是关于k状态的选定通讯员
this will be the chosen correspondent about k-state
about k-state sharing some mineral child by carrying
通过携带来分享一些矿物的孩子，也可以携带一些变体
sharing some mineral child by carrying that's carrying some variants also fits
that's carrying some variants also fits all and we're going to have to compute
全部，我们将必须计算所有的均值和方差
all and we're going to have to compute all the means and the variances of the
all the means and the variances of the observation model for each of the k
每个k空间的观测模型，但密歇根州（如果这是
observation model for each of the k space but michigan if this is the
space but michigan if this is the discrete model can be a multi newly
离散模型可以是一个多新分布，所以我们必须计算
discrete model can be a multi newly distribution so we have to calculate the
distribution so we have to calculate the probabilities of the different states as
一般情况下，我也在监督不同州的概率
probabilities of the different states as well I'm supervising this in general
well I'm supervising this in general like that ok so so tell me what do we
这样好吧，所以告诉我我们在这里有什么
like that ok so so tell me what do we have here
have here so I'm looking at the emission
所以我正在观察排放概率，我们观察到了中国
so I'm looking at the emission probabilities this we observe a chinois
probabilities this we observe a chinois deluxe step 10 all right and it
豪华的第10步好了，它的下一个香味来自该型号
deluxe step 10 all right and it next scent comes from this model this
next scent comes from this model this probability papyrus ink is DNA and DNA
纸莎草墨水是DNA和DNA等于现在的概率发生在一个步骤
probability papyrus ink is DNA and DNA equal to now happens when a step and
equal to now happens when a step and almost if I would say I mean on state K
几乎可以说我的意思是在状态K上，所以如果我在花洞中等于
almost if I would say I mean on state K so if I'm on spent cave is equal to one
so if I'm on spent cave is equal to one so the parameters basically that define
所以这些参数基本上定义了参数的观察模型
so the parameters basically that define the observation models of the parameters
the observation models of the parameters PK and this is what we need to observe
PK，这是我们需要观察的内容，基本上需要完成的内容
PK and this is what we need to observe what we need to complete basically what
what we need to complete basically what we do Emily you're measuring current
艾米丽（Emily），您正在测量电流
[掌声]
what we need to complete basically what we do Emily you're measuring current
[Applause]
分布在两个观察到的变量上，我称之为所有
distribution at both the observed variables and I call all of this
variables and I call all of this variable sex so from next one to X
可变性别，因此从下一个到X大写T和G 1 2 G大写
variable sex so from next one to X capital T and G 1 2 G capital in your
capital T and G 1 2 G capital in your subscript a is the initial probability
下标a是状态和状态的这种转变的初始概率
subscript a is the initial probability of this transitions of the state and the
of this transitions of the state and the observation model 3d panel it is
观察模型3d面板很难像您从我们看到的那样
observation model 3d panel it is difficult as you can see from what we
difficult as you can see from what we have seen on a Markov model here where
在马尔可夫模型上看到过，这是一个难题吗
have seen on a Markov model here where is this a difficult problem
您可以打开左侧与我们在市场上有什么不同的地方
you can open the left hand side what is different from what we had in the market
different from what we had in the market Walden
瓦尔登
你记得在马尔可夫链中，我们有观察性的可能性
different from what we had in the market Walden
you remember in a Markov chain we had the likelihood of the observation sex
你记得在马尔可夫链中，我们有观察性的可能性
the likelihood of the observation sex but now here I have the joint likelihood
但是现在我在给定参数和什么的情况下有X和Z的联合可能性
but now here I have the joint likelihood of X and Z given the parameters and what
of X and Z given the parameters and what is different here
班加西在这里不一样，我们不知道这眼泪
is different here Benghazi we don't know this tears on
Benghazi we don't know this tears on itself so basically this joint look like
本身，所以基本上这个联合的外观看起来会很好
itself so basically this joint look like it would it looks nice
it would it looks nice it looks exactly like an operating model
它看起来完全像一个运营模型，但不幸的是，它们具有的状态
it looks exactly like an operating model but unfortunately the states they have
but unfortunately the states they have not known so we cannot go and do an
不知道，所以我们不能去做一个艾米丽，你将无法正常工作
not known so we cannot go and do an Emily on this you will not work right
因为看起来非常容易观察和操作，但是我们不
because it looks very this is very easy to look at and manipulate but we don't
to look at and manipulate but we don't know what saves so let's go to slide
知道可以节省多少钱，所以让我们滑到70号幻灯片，看看如何计算
know what saves so let's go to slide undred 70 and see on how we can compute
undred 70 and see on how we can compute all these unknown parameters hmm
所有这些未知参数hmm，以便我们在去年春季介绍了
all these unknown parameters hmm so that we covered in last spring and
so that we covered in last spring and I'm going to review it basically in the
我将基本上在hmm的背景下进行审查
I'm going to review it basically in the context of the hmm
context of the hmm is optimized maximized not the hood the
优化最大化而不是观察的可能性的联合
is optimized maximized not the hood the joint of likelihood of the observations
joint of likelihood of the observations of the hidden body most but the
最隐蔽的身体，但对可能性联合的期望
of the hidden body most but the expectation of the joint of likelihood
expectation of the joint of likelihood with respect to the posterior
关于给定的腰部Z的后验分布
with respect to the posterior distribution of Z given live the waist
distribution of Z given live the waist of self and of course the posterior
的自我，当然派生勃起的后验分布是
of self and of course the posterior distribution of derivatives erections is
distribution of derivatives erections is not now because we don't know the
不是现在，因为我们不知道参数，所以我们要做的是
not now because we don't know the parameters so what we're gonna do is
parameters so what we're gonna do is we're gonna try to Eternity we update
我们将尝试永恒，我们将如下更新参数
we're gonna try to Eternity we update the parameters as follows we're going to
the parameters as follows we're going to take some previous iteration takes
进行一些先前的迭代，使部门获得一些值，然后尝试
take some previous iteration takes department some values and then try to
department some values and then try to compute this for strain of
然后用气压计计算出颈部的应变
compute this for strain of the necks with a barometer speaks then
the necks with a barometer speaks then compute the expectation of the join of
计算生计的期望值而不是此参数
compute the expectation of the join of livelihood and not as this parameters
livelihood and not as this parameters here are parameters that are known and
这是已知的参数，我将要更新，所以首先我要
here are parameters that are known and I'm going to update so first I'm going
I'm going to update so first I'm going to compute this expectation using this
使用此后验来计算期望值，该后验值使用
to compute this expectation using this posterior that is approximated using
posterior that is approximated using some the previous iteration of the
一些先前的参数迭代，然后一旦我计算了一下
some the previous iteration of the parameters and then once I compute this
parameters and then once I compute this I am going to maximize this with respect
我将针对参数theta最大化此设置，应该是
I am going to maximize this with respect to parameters theta okay supposedly I am
to parameters theta okay supposedly I am going to abuse the complexity that has
会滥用与我不知道Z有关的复杂性
going to abuse the complexity that has to do with the fact that I don't know Z
to do with the fact that I don't know Z by reducing the joining applied the
通过减少连接，应用了情感G但以某种方式改变了
by reducing the joining applied the affections G but somehow transforming
affections G but somehow transforming the optimization and iterative
谁曾做过的优化和迭代优化问题
the optimization and iterative optimization problem who have worked
optimization problem who have worked with the expectation of the Journal of
与《 Journal of可能性期望》有关的期望
with the expectation of the Journal of likelihood expectation with respect to
likelihood expectation with respect to this posterior and somehow it ray all
此后验光以相同的方式照射所有参数theta
this posterior and somehow it ray all the parameters theta and at the same
the parameters theta and at the same time updating this posterior of Z makes
时间更新Z的后验有一点意义
time updating this posterior of Z makes a little sense
a little sense so this is sort of the final
所以这是最终的期望最大化算法
so this is sort of the final expectation-maximization algorithm to
expectation-maximization algorithm to ensure the problems we have parameters
确保我们有参数的问题，并且您有一些隐藏的变量正确
ensure the problems we have parameters and you have some hidden variables right
但以某种方式我直接与民生杂志合作
but somehow I'm working directly with the journal of livelihood is a much
the journal of livelihood is a much easier proposition than working with the
命题比处理似然效应容易，我的意思是你可以
easier proposition than working with the likelihood effects I mean you can
likelihood effects I mean you can imagine here if you put destinations
想象一下，如果您将目的地作为目的地，则在此分布上
imagine here if you put destinations they dialect on this distribution this
they dialect on this distribution this is computationally intractable you
在计算上很棘手，您无法做任何事情，好吧，您知道
is computationally intractable you cannot do anything about okay you know
cannot do anything about okay you know in this field you come up with Paniagua
在此领域中，您稍后会提出Paniagua，但这尤其是当您
in this field you come up with Paniagua later but this is especially when you
later but this is especially when you take the long this is a very easy
花很长时间，这是一个非常容易的分布，取平均值为
take the long this is a very easy distribution taking the average with
distribution taking the average with respect to this posterior is going to be
关于这个后验将变得容易，这里的关键是计算
respect to this posterior is going to be easy and the key thing here is compute
easy and the key thing here is compute this posterior in tentatively using an
暂时使用这些变量的开始
this posterior in tentatively using an onset of the variables of these
onset of the variables of these parameters and then when you do this
参数，然后在计算此消亡量Q时进行计算
parameters and then when you do this computation of this quantity Q of demise
computation of this quantity Q of demise with respect to theta then come back and
关于theta，然后回来，他们穿着非常漂亮的计算背心
with respect to theta then come back and they dressed very compute vest take
they dressed very compute vest take another optimization with respect to
关于theta的另一种优化，所以这双嘴唇要我们计算
another optimization with respect to theta so this lips want us to compute
theta so this lips want us to compute this expectation that base that second
这种期望基于第二个方面对theta的更多尊重，并希望
this expectation that base that second much much respect to theta and hopefully
much much respect to theta and hopefully you will achieve some convergence in a
您将在短时间内达成一些共识，我们将讨论您所知道的
you will achieve some convergence in a few duration we discuss you know for
few duration we discuss you know for change them and we did this with a
改变它们，我们用一个结点树做这个，好吧，当它出现时
change them and we did this with a junction tree etc okay it comes out when
junction tree etc okay it comes out when you calculate this expectation of the
您可以计算出可能需要的关节的期望值
you calculate this expectation of the joint of likelihood you're gonna need
joint of likelihood you're gonna need some sufficient statistics and those
一些足够的统计数据，而这些足够的统计数据基本上会
some sufficient statistics and those sufficient statistics basically will
sufficient statistics basically will abilities that we have computed from the
我们从前传和后传大师计算出的能力
abilities that we have computed from the forward and backward passing masters
forward and backward passing masters algorithms so the sufficient statistics
算法，所以我们需要的足够统计量就是这个概率
algorithms so the sufficient statistics that we will need is this probability
that we will need is this probability okay and so it is all of the day time
好的，所以整天都是从实际文本复制文本的火车
okay and so it is all of the day time the train from actual text copy text
the train from actual text copy text with subscript capital T so this is the
下标大写T，所以这是给我的平滑分布
with subscript capital T so this is the smoothing distribution that gives me the
smoothing distribution that gives me the trait if they given all my exist with a
特质，如果他们给了我所有，并且存在一个参数空间，我提醒
trait if they given all my exist with a parameter space alright and I remind
parameter space alright and I remind field of symbol we use for ballistic
我们用于弹道的符号字段，这是街区正在运行的西装上
field of symbol we use for ballistic this is the block was running on a suit
this is the block was running on a suit not the beta masters right this is this
不是beta大师，这是ZT的这种动态分布，因为所有
not the beta masters right this is this moving distribution of ZT given all the
moving distribution of ZT given all the data and the other sufficient statistics
数据和我们将需要的其他足够的统计数据可能是联合的
data and the other sufficient statistics we will need is the joint probably
we will need is the joint probably distribution of of ZT minus prong n CP
给定数据的ZT减去叉n CP的分布，所以这是关节
distribution of of ZT minus prong n CP given to the data so this is the joints
given to the data so this is the joints moving distribution that gives me Z at t
移动分布使我与GP一起在t减去1时得到Z
moving distribution that gives me Z at t minus 1 jointly with GP so if you
minus 1 jointly with GP so if you support that to compute this path and do
支持计算此路径并进行此专业计算
support that to compute this path and do this ex-professional calculation you
this ex-professional calculation you will need to compute these two
将需要计算这两个概率，这需要
will need to compute these two probabilities and that requires a
probabilities and that requires a calculation of messages and this
计算消息，这基本上需要
calculation of messages and this basically requires
basically requires with message calculation okay so
消息计算还可以，所以请记住，是的，他的一条消息是
with message calculation okay so remember so yes with one of his messages
remember so yes with one of his messages are coming if you want to find the
如果您想在模型中找到参数，那么就快来了
are coming if you want to find the parameters in your model you have not
parameters in your model you have not choice in the yellow algorithm but the
黄色算法中的选择，但计算器为前进和后退
choice in the yellow algorithm but the calculator is forward and backward
calculator is forward and backward passing messages and when a certain
传递消息以及这些事情的某个特定时刻到来时，
passing messages and when a certain point of these things are coming but
point of these things are coming but rightousness
正义，这是全局
rightousness this is the big picture so let me just
this is the big picture so let me just put a plot here the Subic make visible
在此处放置一个图，使Subic变得可见，基本上您从以下一些值开始
put a plot here the Subic make visible basically you start with some values of
basically you start with some values of the parameters you know there's lots of
您知道的参数有很多我们想从中使用的指导
the parameters you know there's lots of guidance we want to use to start with if
guidance we want to use to start with if you compute this posterior ok of
您可以根据给定的所有数据来计算这种过高的后验
you compute this posterior ok of overstates given all the data in the
overstates given all the data in the previous parameters you calculate this
以前的参数，您可以计算此数量Q，即正态分布
previous parameters you calculate this quantity Q which is the sexpectations
quantity Q which is the sexpectations force here of the joint log likelihood
强制在此处记录联合对数似然，但您在此处注意到对数
force here of the joint log likelihood but you notice here in the log
but you notice here in the log likelihood you have no power
可能你没有权力没事，所以当我得到他所做的一切
likelihood you have no power all right so whatever he did when I get
all right so whatever he did when I get is going to be a function of theta then
将是theta的函数，然后在m步上最大化您的尊重
is going to be a function of theta then on the m-step you maximize with respect
on the m-step you maximize with respect to theta
如果完成转换，则转换为theta
to theta if you convert if you are done if not
if you convert if you are done if not you come back you update the parameters
你回来，更新参数，计算出新的后验，然后吃
you come back you update the parameters you compute a new posterior and you eat
you compute a new posterior and you eat a new expectation of the joint of
对您可能做到的最大可能性的联合的新期望
a new expectation of the joint of likelihood you maximize that you can do
likelihood you maximize that you can do anything you want okay I want you to
任何你想要的好吧，我希望你看看这个表情，所以你们
anything you want okay I want you to look at this expression and so you guys
look at this expression and so you guys can see it again alright so this is the
可以再次看到它，所以这是向后移动的消息
can see it again alright so this is the backward message is this moving
backward message is this moving posterior of c30
C30的后部还好，您还记得城市
posterior of c30 all right and you remember city
因此，例如，如果孩子等于1，则您知道这等于
so for example if the kids are equal to 1 you know what this is equal to is the
1 you know what this is equal to is the probability those little TJ would make
那些小TJ会对我们产生影响的可能性，但这也是对
probability those little TJ would make onto our but is also the expectation of
onto our but is also the expectation of the Zeta TJ why because if a TJ can only
Zeta TJ为什么因为如果TJ只能拿一个是零或一
the Zeta TJ why because if a TJ can only take one is zero or one
让我再次解释这一点，所以这是向量ZT正确，但这可能需要
let me explain this again right so this is a vector Z T right but this can take
is a vector Z T right but this can take values the CP you know why do whatever
珍视CP，您知道为什么此时我拥有任何状态
values the CP you know why do whatever states I have I have at this time I have
states I have I have at this time I have K different states right so I can write
正确的K个州，所以我可以用更简单的部分和一份牛排来写
K different states right so I can write this in a more easier part and a steak
this in a more easier part and a steak well now obviously PJ which is the
现在好了，显然PJ就是ztj基本上相等的概率
well now obviously PJ which is the probability basically of ztj being equal
probability basically of ztj being equal to one in a claim that that is actually
有人声称这实际上是z TJ的期望，因为他
to one in a claim that that is actually the expectation of z TJ because he
the expectation of z TJ because he visited J can take varnish only one and
拜访的J只能涂清漆一加零的行业与
visited J can take varnish only one and zero the profession is the same as the
zero the profession is the same as the probability West so effectively what I
韦斯特如此有效地表达了我的期望，那就是对此的期望
probability West so effectively what I claim is that the expectation of this
claim is that the expectation of this alright is the same community simply
好的，是同一个社区，只是因为他厌倦了英语，
alright is the same community simply because he fatigues English that the
because he fatigues English that the clay has the varnish one of zero okay so
黏土的清漆为零好，所以和接缝的树
clay has the varnish one of zero okay so just and the tree which is the joints
just and the tree which is the joints moving distribution of ZT minus 1 and GT
ZT减1和GT的移动分布，它们的确是别的
moving distribution of ZT minus 1 and GT they are really nothing else the
they are really nothing else the posterior expectations of the z TJ
z TJ变量的后验期望记住我的定义
posterior expectations of the z TJ variable remember that my definition of
variable remember that my definition of gamma J right what was it the first
γJ对，它的第一周期分布是什么的后验
gamma J right what was it the first period distribution is the posterior of
period distribution is the posterior of Z that they given all my data
Z他们给了我所有数据
先生。使命社会对米切尔太平洋的期望是因为忘记了
period distribution is the posterior of Z that they given all my data
mr. mission social expectation of Mitchell Pacific a values because forget
先生。使命社会对米切尔太平洋的期望是因为忘记了
Mitchell Pacific a values because forget about it so this is also the expectation
关于它，所以这也是期望，所以你可以在这里看这个方程
about it so this is also the expectation so can you look at this equation here
so can you look at this equation here now and tell me how from this equation
现在，告诉我如何从等式中获取对数，然后得到期望值
now and tell me how from this equation when I take logs and then expectation I
when I take logs and then expectation I get this equation from what did that
从我认为假设是什么得出的等式
get this equation from what did that come from I think the assumption is and
come from I think the assumption is and this nice equation with the transition
这个很好的方程，具有向右边界过渡的概率，并且
this nice equation with the transition probabilities to a boundary right and
probabilities to a boundary right and you know we can do this the same thing
你知道我们可以在那做同样的事情，但是我怎么得到语法
you know we can do this the same thing there but how how did I get a grammar
there but how how did I get a grammar there let's go to think of this now they
现在让我们考虑一下，他们正在给Rama什么是0k
there let's go to think of this now they are giving Rama what is 0k
这也是z1k的后验，所以他们怎么
this is also that is the posterior expectation of the z1k so how did they
expectation of the z1k so how did they welcome this time to a gamma x level PK
欢迎这次来到伽玛X级PK
记住，这个终端曾经是戏剧，仍然期望他们
expectation of the z1k so how did they welcome this time to a gamma x level PK
remember this terminal used to be the drama still anticipate that their
记住，这个终端曾经是戏剧，仍然期望他们
the drama still anticipate that their indicator function that 0 and K is equal
0和K等于L的指标函数可以给您期望以及
indicator function that 0 and K is equal to L can give you expectation and what
to L can give you expectation and what is that the expectation is gamma Z 1 K
是期望是伽玛Z 1 K，所以从
is that the expectation is gamma Z 1 K so similarly this in the transition from
so similarly this in the transition from t minus 1 to 3 you will get basically
t减去1到3，您将基本上得到这个量K，这就是电动机
t minus 1 to 3 you will get basically this quantity K which is this motoring
this quantity K which is this motoring joining posterior of z t minus 1 and t
连接zt减1和t的后验，这实际上是什么
joining posterior of z t minus 1 and t so what is this actually
so what is this actually this is expectation of what distribution
这是好莱坞的预期分布
this is expectation of what distribution and in the Hollywood
这是城市的联合分布-朗德尔州a和城市是一个斑点
this is the joint distribution of city - rondell states a and city being a speck
rondell states a and city being a speck a the proceeded expectation of that is
对此的预期是Vista的数量T好的，因此养老金
a the proceeded expectation of that is Vista the quantity T okay so the pension
Vista the quantity T okay so the pension is right but this van that we completed
是正确的，但是我们完成了一次交换，我们将其定义为
is right but this van that we completed an exchange that we defined them as
an exchange that we defined them as posterior distributions all right this
后分布好的，这就是我们如何定义它们的方式
posterior distributions all right this is how we define them okay this vectors
is how we define them okay this vectors because if he can take value 1
因为如果他可以取值1，你知道我有不同的K状态
because if he can take value 1 you know I have different K State okay
you know I have different K State okay so when I simplify this and I'm asking
所以当我简化这个，我问什么是祖母的GP k是
so when I simplify this and I'm asking what is grandma's GP k yes that is the
what is grandma's GP k yes that is the posterior of ZT k being equal to on but
ZT k的后验等于on，但也是z TK的个人期望
posterior of ZT k being equal to on but is also the personal expectation of z TK
is also the personal expectation of z TK similarly when I put this Z to minus 1 3
类似地，当我将Z减为1 3和c TK时，是
similarly when I put this Z to minus 1 3 and c TK yes that is the probability for
and c TK yes that is the probability for stated probability of city - Ron being
陈述的城市概率-罗恩（Ron）说为J，而这个州在K状态，
stated probability of city - Ron being of say J and this being of state K but
of say J and this being of state K but is also the personal expectation of was
也是个人的期望被吞噬，所以当你采取这种联合
is also the personal expectation of was devoured and so when you take this joint
devoured and so when you take this joint of livelihood right you take the joint
权的权利，你采取的可能性，你会得到这个
of livelihood right you take the joint of likelihood you will get this
of likelihood you will get this indicator functions from the front when
当您编写任何JK时，指示器的功能从正面开始，在顶部
indicator functions from the front when you write this any JK and on the top
you write this any JK and on the top level get the indicator function that
级别获得城市-Sean J等于1和Z 2 k等于的指标函数
level get the indicator function that city - Sean J equal to 1 and Z 2 k equal
city - Sean J equal to 1 and Z 2 k equal to 1 then when you take this will come
到1，那么当您服用时，您就会知道对该酒的期望
to 1 then when you take this will come in you know expectation of that wine
in you know expectation of that wine expectations because we say that we do
期望，因为我们说我们不与可能性联合
expectations because we say that we do not operate with the joint of likelihood
not operate with the joint of likelihood we have to take expectations
我们必须抱有期望
好吧，我们必须对Z的后验和
not operate with the joint of likelihood we have to take expectations
okay we have to take expectation with respect to the posterior of Z and those
好吧，我们必须对Z的后验和
respect to the posterior of Z and those expectations give you basically the
期望基本上会给您足够的统计数据和足够的数据
expectations give you basically the sufficient statistics and the sufficient
sufficient statistics and the sufficient statistics come to be nothing else but
统计信息什么都没有，只有这个，然后再传给这个伽玛和这个
statistics come to be nothing else but this before message this gamma and this
this before message this gamma and this so this is moving distribution basically
所以这基本上是运动分布，ZT的关节后减-1
so this is moving distribution basically and the joint posterior of ZT minus 1
and the joint posterior of ZT minus 1 and ZT and I have female think here for
ZT和我有女性认为这里是用于观察的手机，所以有
and ZT and I have female think here for the observation mobile so there's
the observation mobile so there's missing energy on the first time I'm
第一次失去能量时我会出现k态
missing energy on the first time I'm going to have k-state
going to have k-state so I'm get the summation here I'm gonna
所以我在这里得到总和，我会正确地得到这个
so I'm get the summation here I'm gonna have this properly
have this properly alright this is this product and I have
好吧，这是这个产品，我已经从同志的个人空间过渡到了
alright this is this product and I have transitioned from gay personal space to
transitioned from gay personal space to carry possible states
携带可能的状态，所以这里是两次加法运算，这是
carry possible states so here the double summation and this is
so here the double summation and this is the sufficient statistics do you get
足够的统计数据可以让您更长的日子吗？如果您得到的话，请在这里
the sufficient statistics do you get longer days okay and here if you get
longer days okay and here if you get again the scan local Christians and this
再次扫描当地的基督徒，这是观察模型的对数
again the scan local Christians and this is the log of the observation model
is the log of the observation model considering the Vermont state flag
考虑到佛蒙特州州旗，所以参数对应
considering the Vermont state flag so the parameters corresponding to
so the parameters corresponding to observation model would be clear big
观测模型将是清晰的大下标K，所以我不知道是否有人
observation model would be clear big subscript K so I don't know if anybody
subscript K so I don't know if anybody remembers but what is the meaning we
记得，但是我们给出的含义是什么
remembers but what is the meaning we have given what is given in the
have given what is given in the literature to this posterior
关于z链的后验概率的文献，我们没有
literature to this posterior probabilities of z chain and we do not
probabilities of z chain and we do not write the expectation of the there was
写出没有z改变而不是公斤的期望
write the expectation of the there was no z change instead of having kilogram
no z change instead of having kilogram of z1 k what did we have on the Markov
z1 k的马尔可夫链上我们记得什么
of z1 k what did we have on the Markov chain remember
记住马尔可夫链上足够的统计数据
remember sufficient statistics on a Markov chain just which is the time the
Markov chain just which is the time the number of times that the first let's say
首先让我们说出您知道家乡状态K的决赛的次数，所以
number of times that the first let's say of the you know final on home state K so
of the you know final on home state K so again that was telling me how many times
再次告诉我多少次
在这里，因为这是一个程序量，所以这是观察数据
of the you know final on home state K so again that was telling me how many times
here because this is a procedure quantity so this is observes the data
在这里，因为这是一个程序量，所以这是观察数据
quantity so this is observes the data right is what is the expectation of the
正确的是我对时间步伐的期望是什么
right is what is the expectation of the times that I will be on on my time step
times that I will be on on my time step one on state K this is what we call the
在状态K上，这就是我们所说的，我们使用的是什么
one on state K this is what we call the what's the matter that we used what is
what's the matter that we used what is used in the literature that we use
在我们专门用于的文献中使用，您会记得自己如何
used in the literature that we use especially for a you remember on how you
especially for a you remember on how you do the am aware if conversion mixtures
是否知道转换是否混合
我在找你知道你会得到频率的鞭子类型的东西，好吧，我知道这是一个
especially for a you remember on how you do the am aware if conversion mixtures
I'm looking you know whip type of things you get frequency okay I know it's a
我在找你知道你会得到频率的鞭子类型的东西，好吧，我知道这是一个
you get frequency okay I know it's a little hard responsibility right and I'm
有点辛苦的责任吧，我正在研究程序中的状态一
little hard responsibility right and I'm looking at state one in a procedure
looking at state one in a procedure setting how many times my state one is I
设置状态数是我的意思是你知道参数然后我
setting how many times my state one is I mean you know the parameter and then I'm
mean you know the parameter and then I'm gonna destroy implying the spy this
会破坏暗示该收款人的间谍，并且该系数在
gonna destroy implying the spy this payee and this coefficients be in the
payee and this coefficients be in the observation model we wanted to work with
我们希望以联合可能性工作的观测模型，因为计算
observation model we wanted to work with a joint likelihood because computation
a joint likelihood because computation is very easy to write this a discrete
编写一个离散模型非常容易，这会说出很多建议
is very easy to write this a discrete model this would say suggestions very
model this would say suggestions very nice okay what years so how can we
好吧，好几年了，那我们怎么才能用我们不知道的东西来计算呢
nice okay what years so how can we compute by what we don't know so there
compute by what we don't know so there this yes the expectation with respect to
这是关于Z右后验的期望，然后他们
this yes the expectation with respect to the posterior of Z right and then they
the posterior of Z right and then they stiffen the complexity but how can I do
加剧了复杂性，但是我如何才能做到这一点，后验取决于
stiffen the complexity but how can I do this well that posterior depends on the
this well that posterior depends on the parameters PI an a and C so the second
参数PI a和C，所以第二步是开始迭代
parameters PI an a and C so the second step is well start iterating on
step is well start iterating on disparities so something didn't compute
差异，因此某些东西无法计算对此的期望
disparities so something didn't compute the expectation of this with respect to
the expectation of this with respect to the posterior given the parameters all
给定参数的后验好的，这就是您在这里看到的
the posterior given the parameters all right this is what you see here then
right this is what you see here then when we have this quantity
当我们把这个数量变成现在的数量时，我们没有
when we have this quantity into this quantity now we didn't take
into this quantity now we didn't take derivatives with respect to Phi K alpha
关于Phi K alpha JK和pre-k权利的导数，以及
derivatives with respect to Phi K alpha JK and with respect to pre-k right and
JK and with respect to pre-k right and we keep doing iteration this is actually
我们继续进行迭代这实际上是第一步，它看起来与
we keep doing iteration this is actually a first step it looks identical to what
a first step it looks identical to what we had for Markov chains there is really
对于马尔可夫链，我们真的没有什么不一样的
we had for Markov chains there is really nothing that is different okay
nothing that is different okay so you can go in to use Lagrange
因此您可以使用拉格朗日乘数来推断
so you can go in to use Lagrange multipliers to infer that the sum of
multipliers to infer that the sum of five K's is equal to one and then take
5个K等于1，然后求导数，我可以告诉你
five K's is equal to one and then take derivatives with this and I can tell you
derivatives with this and I can tell you this research on these maximization step
这些针对这些最大化步骤的研究与我们所做的工作完全相同
this research on these maximization step the suit is identical to what we did for
the suit is identical to what we did for a Markov chain but the the medium of the
马尔可夫链，但单身人士的媒介将大不相同
a Markov chain but the the medium of the singles is very different coming to be
好的
okay
/在任何状态下，Varnum时代的原始责任都不相同
/ this pristine responsibilities of the time Varnum in any state vary from one
time Varnum in any state vary from one to K and similarly energy H is defined
到K，类似地，能量H由后过渡定义
to K and similarly energy H is defined by the posterior transition
by the posterior transition probabilities that so this patient a JK
使得该患者为JK的概率，但在时间t减去一组中的一个
probabilities that so this patient a JK so but at time t minus one among set
so but at time t minus one among set among state J and then I transitional
在状态J中，然后我将时间T过渡到状态k，所以这恰好是
among state J and then I transitional time T to state k so this is exactly
time T to state k so this is exactly what we had before the only difference
我们之前所拥有的唯一区别是，该基因伽玛在​​我们的后
what we had before the only difference is that this gene gamma our posterior
is that this gene gamma our posterior probabilities and there's nothing
概率，没有任何概率，因为这里要计算
probabilities and there's nothing probabilities because here to calculate
probabilities because here to calculate gamma and your current flow the data
伽马和您的电流从时间流逝的数据让我们一直说1或0
gamma and your current flow the data from time let's say 1 or 0 all the way
from time let's say 1 or 0 all the way to capital T okay
到首都T好吧，所以这个人的吸烟概率不是
to capital T okay so this one's smoking probabilities not
so this one's smoking probabilities not predictive probability stress not
预测概率压力不是您知道的可以留在这里的东西
predictive probability stress not something you know you can stay up here
something you know you can stay up here and estimate what this is okay series
并估计这是什么好系列，然后您说现在可以
and estimate what this is okay series alright and then you say now can you
alright and then you say now can you tell me what the expectation when the
告诉我，当z1 K的概率等于1且
tell me what the expectation when the probability of z1 K being equal to 1 and
probability of z1 K being equal to 1 and is given by this entity so that will
是由该实体提供的，因此可以为您提供PI K etcetera etcetera
is given by this entity so that will give you PI K etcetera etcetera
give you PI K etcetera etcetera and insanity enclosures because he's run
和精神错乱的围栏，因为他正在为日历奔跑，你又如何
and insanity enclosures because he's run for the calendars and how do you
for the calendars and how do you calculate
计算
所以这是有可能的，因为我正在对我的所有数据进行计数
for the calendars and how do you calculate
so this is a possibility because I am counting all of the data right in my
所以这是有可能的，因为我正在对我的所有数据进行计数
counting all of the data right in my stickers and I'm waiting them with these
贴纸，我在等这些概率，它们在后面
stickers and I'm waiting them with these probabilities which are the posterior
probabilities which are the posterior probabilities and similarly for the
概率，并且对于方差基本上类似，就像您知道的一样
probabilities and similarly for the variance basically it is like you know
variance basically it is like you know you're estimating a Gaussian alright you
您正在估算高斯，就可以使用所有数据
you're estimating a Gaussian alright you are using all the data okay
are using all the data okay this is with respect to this mean by the
顺便说一下，这是关于这个意思的
this is with respect to this mean by the way all right
way all right this is very important and again your
这非常重要，同样，您的晶圆相对于
this is very important and again your wafers with respect to the
wafers with respect to the responsibilities that the data time T
数据时间T属于theta的职责，您可以将其扩展到
responsibilities that the data time T belongs to theta you can extend this to
belongs to theta you can extend this to actually to the distribution so if you
实际上是分布，所以如果您有多项式或伯努利
actually to the distribution so if you have a multinomial or Bernoulli
have a multinomial or Bernoulli distribution many other things work you
分配很多其他的东西，你可以用我的代数来工作
distribution many other things work you can work the algebra by the way is I'm
can work the algebra by the way is I'm going to go back and bring it to the
要回去基本上把它带到需要，所以完成吸烟
going to go back and bring it to the need basically so completing the smoking
need basically so completing the smoking distributions so you people think is
分布，所以您认为人们认为这是有效的分布
distributions so you people think is working distributions
working distributions sort of
然后，您知道谁想要使用所有
sort of then you know who wants to use all the
then you know who wants to use all the data we are interested in online
我们对在线估算感兴趣的数据，但是您可以查看何时
data we are interested in online estimation right but you can see when if
estimation right but you can see when if you do the expectation-maximization
你要做期望最大化算法，你真的需要这个
you do the expectation-maximization algorithm you really need to have this
algorithm you really need to have this posterior responsibilities and disjoint
后继责任和不连贯的期望，以及那些要求您
posterior responsibilities and disjoint expectations and those required that you
expectations and those required that you use all the data so there's nothing
使用所有数据，所以没有分布，所以我们将讨论如何
use all the data so there's nothing distributions so we'll discuss on how
distributions so we'll discuss on how with message-passing we can compute them
通过消息传递，我们可以计算它们，我将在最佳情况下进行练习
with message-passing we can compute them I'm going to practice like the best when
I'm going to practice like the best when I look at them to acquire the things
我看着他们来获得看起来很复杂的东西，但是我
I look at them to acquire the things looking they're very complicated but I
looking they're very complicated but I think in many ways the hmm model is the
从很多方面考虑，嗯模型是最简单的方法，所以您应该投资一些
think in many ways the hmm model is the simplest okay so you should invest some
simplest okay so you should invest some time to understand
是时候了解